

Johnny Roger Demadara

Fullstack Developer

Contact

Address

Tacurong, Province Of Sultan Kudarat, PH 9800

Phone

+639972430944

E-mail

jrdemadara@protonmail.co m

www

https://www.linkedin.com/in/johnny-roger-demadara-b2b330322/

WWW

https://github.com /jrdemadara

www

https://jrdemadara.dev

WWW

Bold Profile

Skills

API Integration

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 5 years of related experience.

Work History

2021-04

2019-06

2021-09 - Fullstack Developer

Current Sultan Kudarat Provincial Capitol, Isulan, Province Of

Sultan Kudarat

Develop internal app for government use.

2020-09 - **Programmer**

121 East, Davao City, Province Of Davao Del Sur Develop an internal desktop app for managing the construction company operations such project

management & purchases.

2019-07 - **Teacher**

2020-07 Notre Dame of Salaman College, Lebak, Province

Of Sultan Kudarat

Tech web development in Highschool and College.

2018-06 - **Programmer**

Department Of Public Works And Highways, Lebak, Province Of Sultan Kudarat, Philippines

Created a desktop app to be use for internal documents management and also some

paperworks.

Education

2015-07 - Bachelor of Science: Information Technology

Notre Dame of Salaman College - Lebak, Province Of Sultan Kudarat, Philippines

Accomplishments

Web Projects

- Portfolio Website https://jrdemadara.dev
- PTMKapamilya https://ptmkapamilya.org/

RESTful APIs development

Application Development

NodeJS

Laravel

VueJS

Tailwind

PostgreSQL

Redis

Kotlin

Linux Server

- Sultan Kudarat Province Official Website https://sultankudaratprovince.gov.ph/
- PTM Appointment https://appointment.ptmkapamilya.org/
- PTM Transportation Request https://request.ptmkapamilya.org/
- Notre Dame of Cotabato https://ndcotabato.info/
- Notre Dame of Parang https://ndparang.info/
- Azitsorog Inc https://azitsoroginc.com/
- Philippines Punong Barangay ID Card Registration
 https://register.azitsoroginc.com/

Mobile & Desktop App

- ReboxPOS
- LGC Merch
- Extrace
- Sultan Kudarat Province GeoApp
- Maguindanano Province GeoApp
- BLS
- Empployee Monitor
- Small Time Lottery
- RTU Api
- Azitsorog ID Now Updater